codywu@chihchin.com • http://chihchin.com

347.822.1971 • San Francisco, CA

Versatile UX/UI designer with strong background in website design and recent Certificate in Management and Business Track from UC-Berkeley. Strong programming skills and team experience designing visually compelling graphics and web applications. Expertise creating and managing websites from concept to completion, including front-end development, architecture, interface design, navigation, page optimization, and marketing. Capable problem solver, skilled at translating business requirements into engaging digital interfaces.

Areas of Expertise include:

- User Interface Design
- Google Analytics
- Information Architecture
- Web Design
- Sketching
- Programming Proficiency

- User Experience Design
- Competitive Analysis
- Usability Testing
- Wireframing
- Hi-fi/Lo-fi Mockups/Prototypes
- Project Management

Professional Experience

Gopackup Inc. · Santa Clara, CA · April 2017 to August 2017

UX Design Intern

Created wireframes, user flows, and section by section RWD prototypes for entire website and magazine, Introduction of Mexico Culture, to guide developers and visual designers. Reported project status directly to CTO and CEO.

 Tools: Xmind, Axure RP8, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe InDesign, Adobe Experience Design, Sublime, Bitbucket, Google Analytics.

Key Accomplishments:

- Conducted analyses of 33 international competitors, comparing pros and cons of user experiences, and cross-analysis of Google Analytics and internal user experience survey.
- Prioritized and developed solutions for work breakdown structure (WBS) based on different main functions.

ChihChin Web Design Studio • Taipei, Taiwan • March 2012 to April 2015

Translated client requirements for a wide variety of clients into user-friendly prototypes, building front-end sites and content management systems. Outsourced relative elements (advertisements, photo shoots, and posters/logos/video design), fostering strong relationships with vendors to achieve high-quality content solutions.

Tools: SwordSoft Layout, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Dreamweaver, Google Analytics, FTP, HTML, CSS, Javascript, PhoneGap, Xmind, Axure

Key Accomplishments:

- Provided exceptional client support, managing project life cycle from initiation to completion, creating accurate and functional code.
- Delivered training and workshops on marketing strategy to nearly 60 designers in RICH Salon Group.

Walt Disney World • Orlando, FL • 07/2009 to 01/2010

Met or exceeded minimum sales requirements for ticket media sales at Animal Kingdom, offering guests tickets from the menu of more than 128 different configurations.

Key Accomplishments:

- Quickly matched guest needs to "right-fit" tickets; demonstrated and sold merchandise in Downtown Disney, handling cash and credit transactions and preparing packages for shipping and delivery.
- Controlled inventory, receiving and stocking deliveries accurately and efficiently.

Education

Certificate: Management and Business Track, 2017

UC Berkeley Extension Core Program (960+ Hours): Entrepreneurship & Project Management + 4 Month Internship GPA 3.54

Bachelor of Design, Interactive Media, 2012

National Taipei University of Technology • Tapiei, Taiwan *GPA 3.92*

Teaching Assistant: Android Mobile Interaction App course, Virtual Reality Application (Unity 3D) course

Bachelor of International Business, 2010

Yuan Ze University • Taoyuan City, Taiwan Student Association of YZU - Vice-minister of PR Dept. Student Association of IB Dept. - Vice-minister of PR Dept.

Awards

Final Project (Leader): (AR)/Game (Unity 3D+Kinect)/Research Document/Ebook/2011 IXDDA Seminar **Carpooling Project:** Cooperation with Dept. of Electronics Engineering Prof. Shih-Chia Huang. Imagine Cup (Jan. 2011) & LongTerm Competition (April 2011)

Magic Mirror Project: Y.S. Award (March 2011), Judges' List Award, Augmented Reality + RFID Prototype Advanpark Project: Cooperation with National Chengchi University & National Taipei University of Education TIC100 Entrepreneur Competition Fourth Prize & Teamwork Award